

 $\searrow$ 

white.wkval@gmail.com

C

+380956131955

6

https://t.me/alexi\_cat

S

https://catwebua.github.io/ale

Q<sub>C</sub>

http://linkedin.com/in/aleksey

### **LANGUAGE**

English A2 (pre-intermediate)

## **EDUCATION**

Kyiv Slavonic University (Kiev) International Relations

2009 - 2016

### **CERTIFICATES**

2017

Administrator of Unix systems

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

#### My hobby

board games, extreme bike cycling (downhill), snowboard and more active fun. Also I like: • heavy music like metal, punk and ska, visit concerts and festivals. • computer games: «Heroes3 WOG», «Killing floor», «StarCraft».

# **ALEXEY YAKOVLEV**

### FRONT-END DEVELOPER

### SUMMARY

Looking for a job as a Front end React developer, I have over year of commercial experience and react courses.

For the last 4 years I have made up sites and implemented functionality and logic in JS.

My Stack

React, TypeScript, JS, GraphQL/Apollo, MaterialUI, HTML, CSS(SCSS), CMS (wordpress), Gulp/Webpack, Bootstrap.

My latest project on react:

https://app.sourc3.xyz

My pet project ToDo List (react, typescript, hooks): https://github.com/catWebua/PetProject\_ToDoList\_React.git

My site portfolio:

https://catwebua.github.io/alexi/

Plus a portfolio of 15 projects in freelance (links on regues)

### SOFTWARE SKILLS

HTML Photoshop/Avocode/Figma

CSS/SCSS BEN

JS GULP/WEBPACK

React/ReactHooks Bootstrap
GraphQL/Apollo MaterialUI

# Experience

POINT Beam | Front-end React Developer

01/2022 - 10/2022

I participated in the development project for Sourc3, used on the project:

- HTML5/CSS, React/ReactHooks, AntDesign.

POINT Demigos | Front-end React Developer

08/2021 - 12/2021

I participated in the development project for tennis tournaments. used on the project:

 $\hbox{- HTML5/CSS, React/ReactHooks, GraphQL/Apollo, Material UI.}\\$ 

Developer Utec Group (utec-group.com) | Front-end Developer

10/2020 - 07/2021

• Site redesign. • Work with hosting and domains. • Create and fill new sites • Testing and bug fixing of existing sites. • Support and revision of the company's websites on wordpress.

ICPA, international marketing agency | Front-end developer 07/2019 - 08/2020

• Site redesign. • Pumping sites. • Sites adaptation for different screen sizes, browsers and devices. • Testing and bug fixing of existing sites.

POINT > entoreactdetka.com | Front-end developer

05/2018 - 06/2019

• Template conversion in HTML code. • Site redesign. • Sites adaptation for different screen sizes, browsers and devices. • Configuring and modification of scripts. • Testing and bug fixing of existing sites.